<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Book Hive</string>
    <string-array name="options">
        <item>Option 1</item>
        <item>Option 2</item>
        <item>Option 3</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="book1_ifo">From Colleen Hoover, the #1 New York Times bestselling author of It Starts with Us and It Ends with Us, a heart-wrenching love story that proves attraction at first sight can be messy. When Tate Collins meets airline pilot Miles Archer, she knows it isn’t love at first sight. They would not even go so far as to consider themselves friends. The only thing Tate and Miles have in common is an undeniable mutual attraction.</string>
    <string name="book2_ifo">Archer\'s Voice is the story of a woman chained to the memory of one horrifying night and the man whose love is the key to her freedom. It is the story of a silent man who lives with an excruciating wound and the woman who helps him find his voice. It is the story of suffering, fate, and the transformative power of love. </string>
    <string name="book3_ifo">Now a movie starring Lucy Hale and Austin Stowell, USA Today bestselling author Sally Thorne’s hilarious and sexy workplace comedy all about that thin, fine line between hate and love.</string>
    <string name="book4_ifo">A Game of Thrones is the first novel in A Song of Ice and Fire, a series of fantasy novels by American author George R. R. Martin. The popularity of this fantasy book has exploded over the last several years, so what list wouldn’t include A Game of Thrones as one of the greatest fantasy series?  It has magic, intrigue, mystery, and lots of romance.</string>
    <string name="book5_ifo">The Fellowship of the Ring is the first of three volumes of the epic novel The Lord of the Rings by the English author J. R. R. Tolkien. The Dark Lord put all of his powers in One Ring that was taken from him. After years in Middle-earth, Bilbo Baggins ends up with the ring. After he reaches his eleventh-first year, he disappears, and the ring becomes the property of Frodo. Thus starts the epic quest to destroy the ring. </string>
    <string name="book6_ifo">The Silent Patient is a 2019 psychological thriller novel written by British–Cypriot author Alex Micheladas’. It is basically a shocking psychological thriller of a woman’s act of violence against her husband as she randomly shoots him five time in the face. And now criminal psychotherapist obsessed with uncovering her motive. </string>
    <string name="book7_ifo">Whose truth is the lie? Stay up all night reading the sensational psychological thriller that has readers obsessed. Lowen Ashleigh is a struggling writer on the brink of financial ruin when she accepts the job offer of a lifetime. Jeremy Crawford, husband of bestselling author Verity Crawford, has hired Lowen to complete the remaining books in a successful series his injured wife is unable to finish. After all, no matter how devoted Jeremy is to his injured wife, a truth this horrifying would make it impossible for him to continue to love her. </string>
    <string name="book8_ifo">A Good Girl\'s Guide to Murder is a young adult mystery debut novel by Holly Jackson. The case is closed. Five years ago, schoolgirl Andie Bell was murdered by Sal Singh. The police know he did it. Everyone in town knows he did it. But having grown up in the same small town that was consumed by the murder, Pippa Fitz-Amobi isn\'t so sure. When she chooses the case as the topic for her final year project, she starts to uncover secrets that someone in town desperately wants to stay hidden. And if the real killer is still out there, how far will they go to keep Pip from the truth? </string>
    <string name="book9_ifo">And Then There Were None is a mystery novel by the English writer Agatha Christie. First, there were ten—a curious assortment of strangers summoned as weekend guests to a little private island off the coast of Devon. Their host, an eccentric millionaire unknown to all of them, is nowhere to be found. All that the guests have in common is a wicked past they\'re unwilling to reveal—and a secret that will seal their fate. Each has been marked for murder. When they realize that murders are occurring as described in the rhyme, terror mounts. One by one they fall prey. Before the weekend is out, there will be none. Who has choreographed this dastardly scheme? And who will be left to tell the tale? Only the dead are above suspicion. </string>
</resources>